[{"cards":[{"answer":"Pediatric vision refers to the visual health and development of children from infancy through adolescence.\n\n","cardId":4,"learned":false,"question":"What is pediatric vision?"},{"answer":"Early detection and treatment of vision problems in children are crucial for their overall development, learning, and quality of life.\n\n","cardId":5,"learned":true,"question":"Why is pediatric vision important?\n\n"},{"answer":"The American Academy of Ophthalmology recommends the first eye exam at around 6 months of age.\n\n","cardId":6,"learned":false,"question":"At what age should a child have their first eye exam?\n\n"}],"setId":1,"setName":"Pediatric Vision"},{"cards":[{"answer":"A retinal disease is a group of eye conditions that affect the retina, the light-sensitive tissue at the back of the eye.","cardId":2,"learned":false,"question":"What is a retinal disease?\n"},{"answer":"Common symptoms may include blurred vision, floaters, flashes of light, and a gradual loss of vision.","cardId":3,"learned":false,"question":"What are common symptoms of retinal diseases?\n"},{"answer":"Common retinal diseases include age-related macular degeneration (AMD), diabetic retinopathy, retinal detachment, and retinitis pigmentosa.","cardId":4,"imgPath":"C:\\Users\\Thu\\OneDrive\\Desktop\\flashrabbit\\src\\cardImages\\481ba26b-39cc-4f52-91cd-04d7187babf1-undefined","learned":false,"question":"What are some common retinal diseases?\n"},{"answer":"Some retinal diseases, like diabetic retinopathy, can be managed through proper control of underlying conditions like diabetes. Regular eye exams can also help detect issues early.","cardId":5,"learned":false,"question":"Can retinal diseases be prevented?\n"}],"learnedCards":0,"setId":2,"setName":"Retinal Disease","totalCards":0},{"cards":[{"answer":"Glaucoma is typically diagnosed through a comprehensive eye exam which may include tonometry (measuring eye pressure), ophthalmoscopy (examining the optic nerve), and visual field testing.\n\n","cardId":1,"learned":false,"question":"How is glaucoma diagnosed?\n","imgPath":"C:\\Users\\Thu\\OneDrive\\Desktop\\flashrabbit\\src\\cardImages\\0c0a97ad-3b1e-4766-b551-1d4a2d8b18dd-undefined"},{"answer":"Yes, glaucoma can be managed and treated to slow down its progression. Treatment options may include eye drops, oral medications, laser therapy, or surgery.\n\n","cardId":2,"learned":false,"question":"Can glaucoma be treated?\n"},{"answer":"While it may not always be preventable, early detection and treatment can help slow or prevent vision loss from glaucoma.\n\n","cardId":3,"learned":false,"question":"Can glaucoma be prevented?\n"},{"answer":"Unfortunately, damage to the optic nerve caused by glaucoma is generally irreversible. However, early detection and treatment can help prevent further vision loss.\n\n","cardId":4,"learned":false,"question":"Is glaucoma reversible?\n"}],"learnedCards":0,"setId":3,"setName":"Glaucoma","totalCards":0}]